Guide to the Gotham Inc. Records, 1967-1997 and undated RL.00468
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1973-1996 and undated, 129 boxes
  - Major Clients, 1973-1996 and undated
    - Ross Laboratories (formerly Abbott Laboratories),1980-1996 and undated
      - Fresh Idea, 1986
        - 1541. Mormar. Ross Laboratories. Ensure. Fresh Idea. XYLC 6113 Meg & Peg :30. 1986 (Box 91)
        - 1542. Mormar. Ross Laboratories. Ensure. Fresh Idea. XYLC 6113 Meg & Peg :30. 1986 (Box 91)
      - Murine, 1982-1985
        - 1543. Mormar. Murine. Ear Drops. LAEA 0304 Only Complete Rev. II :30. 1982 (Box 91)
        - 1544. Mormar. Murine. Ear Drops. LAEA 0304 Only Complete Rev. II :30. 1982 (Box 91)
        - 1545. Mormar. Murine. Ear Drops. LAEA 0304 Only Complete Rev. II :30. 1982 (Box 91)
        - 1546. Mormar. Murine. Ear Drops. LAEA 9675 Only Complete Way :30. 1984 (Box 91)
        - 1547. Mormar. Murine. Ear Drops. LAEA 8454 Cotton Swabs :30; LAEA 8486 Medical Fact :30. 1984 (Box 91)
        - 1548. Mormar. Murine. Ear Wax Removal System. LAEA 5043 Spokesman in ear Version 1 :30. 1985 (Box 91)
        - 1549. Mormar. Murine. Ear Wax Removal System. LAEA 5043 Spokesman in ear Version 1 :30. 1985 (Box 91)
      - Murine (continued), 1985-1991 (Box 92)
        - 1550. Laurence Charles & Free. Ross Laboratories. Murine. Earwax System. 6 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1985 (Box 92)
        - 1551. Laurence Charles & Free. Ross Laboratories. Murine. Earwax System. 6 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1985 (Box 92)
        - 1552. Mormar. Murine. Ear Wax Removal System. LAEA 5043 Spokesman in Ear Vers.1 :30. 1985 (Box 92)
        - 1553. Murine Ear. Spokesman in Ear; Spokesman in Ear Rev. 1987 (Box 92)
        - 1554. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Murine. Ear Drops. LAEA 7053 :30. 1987 (Box 92)
        - 1555. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Murine. Ear Drops. Single Swimmer :15; Swimmer-SFX Vers. :15. 1988 (Box 92)
        - 1556. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Murine. Ear Wax System. LAEA 7085 Spokesman in Ear Rev. :15. 1988 (Box 92)
        - 1557. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Murine. Ear Drops. LAEA 7185 US Swim Team-Women :15. 1988 (Box 92)
        - 1558. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Murine. Ear Drops. LAEA 7115 US Swim Team Medley :15. 1988 (Box 92)
        - 1559. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Murine. Ear Drops. LAEA 7115 US Swim Team Medley :15. 1988 (Box 92)
        - 1560. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Murine. Ear Wax System. LAEA 7085 Spokesman in Ear Rev. :15. 1988 (Box 92)
        - 1561. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Murine. Ear Drops. LAEA 7195 Spokesman in Ear New Product :15. 1989 (Box 92)
        - 1562. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Murine. Ear Drops. LAEA 0235 Spokesman/New Product :15; LAEA 0245 US Swim team-Medley/New Product :15; LAEA 0255 US Swim team-Women/New Product :15. 1990 (Box 92)
        - 1563. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Murine. Ear Drops. LAEA 0235 Spokesman/New Product :15; LAEA 0245 US Swim team-Medley/New Product :15; LAEA 0255 US Swim team-Women/New Product :15. 1990 (Box 92)
        - 1564. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Murine. Ear Drops. 5 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1991 (Box 92)
        - 1565. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Murine. Ear Drops. LAEA 1261 Women's Swim Team :10; LAEA 1281 Spokesman in Ear Rev. :10. 1991 (Box 92)
      - Murine (continued), 1991-1993 (Box 93)
        - 1566. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Murine. Ear Drops. LAEA 1261 Women's Swim Team :10; LAEA 1281 Spokesman In Ear Rev.1 :10. 1991 (Box 93)
        - 1567. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Murine. LAEA 3315 It's Here Rev.3 :15; LAEA 3325 Cotton Swabs Ver.7 Rev. :15. 1993 (Box 93)
        - 1568. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Murine. LAEA 3315 It's Here Rev.3; LAEA 3325 Cotton Swabs Ver.7 Rev.; LAEA0253 Spokesman. 1993 (Box 93)
        - 1569. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Murine. LAEA 3315 It's Here Rev.3 :15; LAEA 3325 Cotton Swabs Ver.7 Rev. :15. 1993 (Box 93)
      - Selicare, 1988
        - 1570. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selicare. XYLC 8073 Salon Rev. :30; XYLC 8063 Twirl Alt. Vers. A :30; Lather :30. 1988 (Box 93)
        - 1571. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selicare. XYLC 8063 Twirl Alt. :30; XYLC 8063 Twirl/Mortice :30. 1988 (Box 93)
        - 1572. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selicare. XYLC 8063 Twirl Alt. Vers. A :30; XYLC 8063 Twirl Alt. Vers. B :30; XYLC 8063 Twirl Alt. Vers. C :30;. 1988 (Box 93)
        - 1573. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. XYLC 8053 Lather :30; Lather Alt. :30. 1988 (Box 93)
      - Selsun, 1980-1981
        - 1574. McCann-Erickson Inc. Abbott Labs. Selsun Blue. LASB 0317 Girl in the Crystal Ball Rev. :30; LASB 0318 Man in the Crystal Ball Rev. :30. 1980 (Box 93)
        - 1575. Daniel & Charles. Abbott Labs. Selsun Blue. LASB 1113 Bottle Effect/Female/CC :30; LASB 1103 Bottle Effect/Male/CC :30. 1981 (Box 93)
        - 1576. Daniel & Charles. Abbott Labs. Selsun Blue. LASB 1113 Bottle Effect/Female/CC :30; LASB 1103 Bottle Effect/Male/CC :30. 1981 (Box 93)
        - 1577. Daniel & Charles. Abbott Labs. Selsun Blue. LASB 1023 Bottle Effect/Female :30. 1981 (Box 93)
        - 1578. Daniel & Charles. Abbott Labs. Selsun Blue. LASB 1053 Bottle Effect/Female/CBS :30. 1981 (Box 93)
        - 1579. Daniel & Charles. Abbott Labs. Selsun Blue. LASB 1153 Bottle Effect/Female Rev.1 :30; LASB 1143 Bottle Effect/Male Rev.1 :30. 1981 (Box 93)
        - 1580. Daniel & Charles. Abbott Labs. Selsun Blue. LASB 1133 Bottle Effect/Female/CBS/CC :30; LASB 1123 Bottle Effect/Male/CBS/CC :30. 1981 (Box 93)
        - 1581. Daniel & Charles. Abbott Labs. Selsun Blue. LASB 1073 Bottle Effect/Male CBS :30; LASB 1093 Bottle Effect/Female/CBS/Rev.1 :30. 1981 (Box 93)
        - 1582. Daniel & Charles. Abbott Labs. Selsun Blue. LASB 1163 Bottle Effect/Male/Rev.II :30;LASB 1173 Bottle Effect/Female Rev.III :30. 1981 (Box 93)
      - Selsun (continued), 1981-1985 (Box 94)
        - 1583. Daniel & Charles. Abbott Labs. Selsun Blue. LASB 1083 Bottle Effects/Female Rev.I :30; LASB 1033 Bottle Effect/Male :30. 1981 (Box 94)
        - 1584. Laurence Charles & Free. Abbott Labs. Selsun Blue. ALSB 2273 Split Screen/Female :30. Undated (Box 94)
        - 1585. Laurence Charles & Free. Abbott Labs. Selsun Blue. ALSB 2273 Split Screen/Female :30; ALSB 2273A Split Screen/Female A :30. 1982 (Box 94)
        - 1586. Laurence Charles & Free. Abbott Labs. Selsun Blue. ALSB 2283 Split Screen/Male. Undated (Box 94)
        - 1587. Selsun Blue. Split Screen/Female. Mixed Track. 1982 (Box 94)
        - 1588. Laurence Charles & Free. Abbott Labs. Selsun Blue. ALSB 3653 Multiplying Man. 1983 (Box 94)
        - 1589. Laurence Charles & Free. Selsun Blue. ALSB 3503 Three People :30. 1983 (Box 94)
        - 1590. Laurence Charles & Free. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1984 (Box 94)
        - 1591. Laurence Charles & Free. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. ALSB 4733 Extra Conditioning Formula/Two Women/Flying Logo Rev.1 :30; ALSB 4733 Extra Conditioning Formula/Two Women/Flying Logo Rev.1 Alt. Vers. :30; ALSB 4723 Extra Conditioning Formula/Selsun-Sational :30. 1984 (Box 94)
        - 1592. Laurence Charles & Free. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. ALSB 4743 Extra Conditioning Formula/Doctors Ordered/Flying Logo :30; ALSB 4733 Extra Conditioning Formula/Two Women/Flying Logo :30. 1984 (Box 94)
        - 1593. Mormar. Selsun Blue. ALSB 3653 :Three People II :30. 1984 (Box 94)
        - 1594. Laurence Charles & Free. Ross Laboratories. Ex-Medicated Selsun Blue. ALSB 5843 Back of Head vers. G/Alt.5 :30. 1985 (Box 94)
        - 1595. Laurence Charles & Free. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. ALSB 5803 3 People Rec/Extra Conditioning Tag :30. 1985 (Box 94)
        - 1596. Laurence Charles & Free. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. ALSB 5843 Back of the Head Vers.D; ALSB 5853 Navy Blazer Vers.D. 1985 (Box 94)
        - 1597. Mormar. Selsun Blue. LASB 0325 Pouring Efficacy :30. 1985 (Box 94)
        - 1598. Mormar. Selsun Blue. ALSB 4753 Two Women Flying Logo Rev.1 :30. 1985 (Box 94)
      - Selsun (continued), 1986-1989 (Box 95)
        - 1599. Daniel & Charles. Selsun Blue. 6 Spots. See Enclosed List. Undated (Box 95)
        - 1600. Mormar. Selsun Blue. ALSB 6033 3 People II/Extra Medicated Rev. :30. 1986 (Box 95)
        - 1601. Laurence Charles & Free. Selsun Blue. ALSB 6123 3 People II Extra Medicated/ABC Vers. :30. 1986 (Box 95)
        - 1602. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. ALSB 6085 # People II :15. 1986 (Box 95)
        - 1603. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. ALSB 6043 Three People 2 Plus Extra Medicated :30. 1986 (Box 95)
        - 1604. Mormar. Selsun Blue. ALSB 6143 3 People II/Extra Medicated Rev.II :30. 1986 (Box 95)
        - 1605. Mormar. Selsun Blue. ALSB 6133 3 People/Faster :30. 1986 (Box 95)
        - 1606. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. ALSB 6965 3 People II :15; ALSB 6023 Celebrity :30; ALSB 6023 Celebrity Alt. :30;. 1986 (Box 95)
        - 1607. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Selsun Blue. ALSB 6973 Blue Bottle/How Serious :30. 1986 (Box 95)
        - 1608. Mormar. Selsun Blue. ALSB 6153 3 People II Extra Medicated Rev.II :30. 1986 (Box 95)
        - 1609. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. Serious Blue Non-New ALSB 7273 :30; ALSB 7285 :15. 1987 (Box 95)
        - 1610. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Selsun Blue. ALSB 7183 3 People/Coupon :30; ALSB 7193 3 People/Coupon ABC :30. 1987 (Box 95)
        - 1611. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Selsun Blue. Serious Blue Non-New ALSB 7273 :30; ALSB 7285 :15. 1987 (Box 95)
        - 1612. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. ALSB 7213 Backstage Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 95)
        - 1613. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. ALSB 7223 Blue is Better (legal) :30; ALSB 7223 Blue is Better :30. 1987 (Box 95)
        - 1614. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Selsun Blue. LASB 9653 Blue is Better--Man Rev. Static :30; LASB 9663 Blue is Better-Women Rev. :30. 1989 (Box 95)
        - 1615. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Selsun Blue. Extra Care. LASB 9563 Let Go of your Chapeau :30. 1989 (Box 95)
      - Selsun (continued), 1989-1991 (Box 96)
        - 1616. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue Extra Care. LASB 9643 Upside Down Alt. Ver. Rev. 2; LASB 9653 Let go of Your Chapeau Rev.2; LASB 9543 Salon Rev.2 3-:30. 1989 (Box 96)
        - 1617. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue Extra Care. LASB 9733 Fresno Hats :30. 1989 (Box 96)
        - 1618. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Selsun Blue. LASB 9633 Blue is Better-Man Rev. Static :30; LASB 9643 Blue is Better-Women Rev. :30. 1989 (Box 96)
        - 1619. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1989 (Box 96)
        - 1620. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue Extra Care. LASB 9733 Fresno Hats :30. 1989 (Box 96)
        - 1621. Mormar. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. LASB 0745 Independent promotion Rev. W/ Oing :15; LASB 0755 Piggyback Announcer rev. W/ Ping :15. 1990 (Box 96)
        - 1622. Mormar. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. LASB 0745 Independent promotion Rev. W/ Oing :15; LASB 0755 Piggyback Announcer rev. W/ Ping :15. 1990 (Box 96)
        - 1623. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue/Murine. 12 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1990 (Box 96)
        - 1624. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Extra Medicated Selsun Blue. LASB 1875 EM/Blue is Better rev. Core :15. 1991 (Box 96)
        - 1625. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Selsun Blue. 4-15 sec spots. See Enclosed List. 1991 (Box 96)
        - 1626. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Extra Medicated Selsun Blue. LASB 1875 EM/Blue is Better rev. Core :15. 1991 (Box 96)
        - 1627. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Extra Medicated Selsun Blue. LASB 1875 EM/Blue is Better rev. Core :15. 1991 (Box 96)
        - 1628. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Extra Medicated Selsun Blue. LASB 0805 EM/Blue is Better/Uh-Uh/Rev. :15. 1991 (Box 96)
        - 1629. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Extra Medicated Selsun Blue. LASB 1875 EM/Blue is Better rev. Core :15. 1991 (Box 96)
        - 1630. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1991 (Box 96)
        - 1631. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. 5-15 Sec Spots. See Enclosed List. 1991 (Box 96)
        - 1632. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. LASB 1815 Independent Promo Rev.2 :15; LASB1845 Blue is Better/Women Rev. ABC :15; LASB 1865 Blue is Better/Man Rev. :15. 1991 (Box 96)
      - Selsun (continued), 1992-1996 (Box 97)
        - 1633. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Gold For Women. LASB 2935 I Know I Should :15; LASB 2925 Gold Tone :15; LASB 2925 Gold Tone-Non Gold :15. 1992 (Box 97)
        - 1634. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Gold For Women. LASB 2025 Gold Tone :15. 1992 (Box 97)
        - 1635. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. LASB 2995 3 People/Non Parity :15. 1992 (Box 97)
        - 1636. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Gold For Women. LASG 2025 Gold Tone :15. 1992 (Box 97)
        - 1637. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. LASB 2995 3 People/Non Parity :15. 1992 (Box 97)
        - 1638. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. LASB 2995 3 People/Non parity :15. 1992 (Box 97)
        - 1639. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Gold For Women. LASG 2025 Gold Tone :15. 1992 (Box 97)
        - 1640. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Gold For Women. LASG 3095 Gold Tone Non New Rev.2 :15. 1993 (Box 97)
        - 1641. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Extra Medicated Selsun Blue. LASB 1875 EM/Blue is Better rev. Core :15. 1993 (Box 97)
        - 1642. Selsun Blue. Morph :15; Selsun Blue :15; Locker Room :15. 1993 (Box 97)
        - 1643. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Selsun Blue. Presentation. See Enclosed List. 1994 (Box 97)
        - 1644. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. LASB 4105 Selsun Power A :15. 1994 (Box 97)
        - 1645. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. LASB 4105 Selsun Power A :15. 1994 (Box 97)
        - 1646. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. LASB 4105 Selsun Power A :15. 1994 (Box 97)
        - 1647. Gotham Inc. Ross Laboratories. Selsun Blue. LASB 6055 Third Base Coach/Wrong Signal :15. 1996 (Box 97)
      - Tronolane, 1982
        - 1648. Laurence Charles & Free. Abbott Labs. Tronolane. 5-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1982 (Box 97)
        - 1649. Laurence Charles & Free. Abbott Labs. Tronolane. LATC 2383 :Tom Morton IV :30. 1982 (Box 97)
      - Trombolane (continued), 1982-1983 (Box 98)
        - 1650. Mormar. Tronolane. LATC 2443 Sue Green Alt. Rev.1 CBS :30; LATC 2433 Tom Morton Rev.6 CBS :30. 1982 (Box 98)
        - 1651. Laurence Charles & Free. Abbott Labs. Tronolane. LATC 2333 Vignettes :30; LATC 2343 Package :30. 1982 (Box 98)
        - 1652. Tronolane. Testimonial G Rev.2; Ticking T. Undated (Box 98)
        - 1653. Mormar. Tronolane. LATC 2443 Sue Green Alt. Rev.1 CBS :30; LATC 2433 Tom Morton Rev.6 CBS :30. 1982 (Box 98)
        - 1654. Laurence Charles & Free. Tronolane. LATC 2403 Tom Morton V :30; LATC 2393 Sue Green :30; LATC 2423 Sue Green Alt. :30. 1982 (Box 98)
        - 1655. Abbott Labs. Tronolane. LATC 2353 Tom Morton II Rev. :30. 1982 (Box 98)
        - 1656. Laurence Charles & Free. Tronolane. Candid. 1982 (Box 98)
        - 1657. Laurence Charles & Free. Abbott Labs. Tronolane. LATC 2393 Sue Green :30. 1982 (Box 98)
        - 1658. Laurence Charles & Free. Abbott Labs. LATC 2373 Tom Morton III :30. 1982 (Box 98)
        - 1659. Mormar. Tronolane. LATC 2353 Tom Morton 2 Rev.2; LATC 2403 Tom Morton 5; LATC 2423 Sue Green Alt. 3-30 Sec. 1983 (Box 98)
      - Vita Steps, 1986
        - 1660. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Vita-Steps. XYLC 6133 McKinneys-Woman :30. 1986 (Box 98)
        - 1661. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Vita-Steps. XYLC 6133 McKinneys-Anncr. :30. 1986 (Box 98)
        - 1662. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Vita-Steps. XYLC 6123 Nutritionist Rev. :30. 1986 (Box 98)
        - 1663. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Vita-Steps. XYLC 6133 McKinneys-Woman :30. 1986 (Box 98)
        - 1664. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Vita-Steps. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. Undated (Box 98)
        - 1665. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Ross Laboratories. Vita-Steps. XYLC 6213 'McKinneys/NBC Rev. :30; XYLC 6223 McKinneys/ABC-CBS Rev. :30. 1986 (Box 98)
    - Thompson Medical,1986-1993 and undated
      - Aqua-Ban, 1988 (Box 99)
        - 1666. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. TSAB 8213 :30; TSAB 8203 :30; TSAB 8175 :15. 1988 (Box 99)
        - 1667. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. TSAB 8203 :30; TSAB 8175 :15. 1988 (Box 99)
        - 1668. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. TSAB 8133 Pitcher Rev. IV CBS; TSAB 8123 Pitcher Rev.III ABC/NBC. 1988 (Box 99)
        - 1669. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. 4-15 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1988 (Box 99)
        - 1670. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. TSAB 8155 Pitcher NBC :15. 1988 (Box 99)
        - 1671. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. TSAB 8165 Pitcher Rev. :15. 1988 (Box 99)
        - 1672. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. TSAB 8123 Pitcher Rev.3 ABC/NBC :30; TSAB 8133 Pitcher Rev.3 CBS :30. 1988 (Box 99)
        - 1673. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. TSAB 8133 Pitcher Rev.3 CBS :30. 1988 (Box 99)
        - 1674. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. Pitcher: TSAB 8253 Rev.6 ABC/CBS W/rev. Prod Shots :30; TSAB 8225 Rev. Vers.2 W/ Original Package :15; TSAB 8235 Rev.3 W/ New Background :15. 1988 (Box 99)
        - 1675. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. TSAB 8213 Pitcher Rev.4 NBC; TSAB 8203 Pitcher Rev.5 ABC/CBS. 1988 (Box 99)
        - 1676. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1988 (Box 99)
        - 1677. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. Calendar :30. 1988 (Box 99)
        - 1678. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. TSAB 8213 Pitcher Rev.4 NBC :30. 1988 (Box 99)
        - 1679. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. Calendar :30. 1988 (Box 99)
        - 1680. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. Pitcher: TSAB 8253 Rev.6 ABC/CBS W/Rev. Prod Shots. :30; TSAB 8225 Rev. Vers.2 W/ Original Package :15; TSAB 8235 Rev.3 W/New Background :15. 1988 (Box 99)
        - 1681. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. TSAB 8225 Pitcher Ver.2 :15. 1988 (Box 99)
      - Aqua-Ban (continued), 1988-1993 (Box 100)
        - 1682. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. TSAB 8185 Pitcher Rev. W/ Original Package :15; TSAB 8195 Pitcher Rev.3 W/ New Background :15. 1988 (Box 100)
        - 1683. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. TSAB 1003 Pitcher Rev.5 :30. 1991 (Box 100)
        - 1684. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aqua-Ban. Reel. 5 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1993 (Box 100)
      - Aspercreme, 1987-1988
        - 1685. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. TSAC 7215 Woman/Odor :15. 1987 (Box 100)
        - 1686. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. XTVI 7045 Woman Rev.3 :15. Undated (Box 100)
        - 1687. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. XTVI 7045 Woman Rev.3 :15. 1987 (Box 100)
        - 1688. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. TSAC 7163 Announcement Rev.1 :30; TSAC 7183 Letter :30. 1987 (Box 100)
        - 1689. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. XTVI 7045 Woman Rev.3 :15. 1987 (Box 100)
        - 1690. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. TSAC 7143 Announcement :30; TSAC 7153 Announcement Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 100)
        - 1691. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. TSAC 8333 No Pills :30; TSAC 8345 No Pills :15. 1988 (Box 100)
        - 1692. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Aspercreme. TSAC 8465 Cottam :15; TSAC 8445 Mc Kee :15; TSAC 8455 Tirrell :15. 1988 (Box 100)
        - 1693. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1988 (Box 100)
        - 1694. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. TSAC 8455 Lois Tirrell; TSAC 8465 Kent Cottam. 1988 (Box 100)
        - 1695. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Aspercreme. Joan Mc Kee :15. 1988 (Box 100)
        - 1696. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Aspercreme. TSAC 8333 No Pills :30; TSAC 8345 No Pills :15. 1988 (Box 100)
        - 1697. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. TSAC 8383 No Pills Rev.5 :30; TSAC 8395 No Pills Rev.5 :15. 1988 (Box 100)
        - 1698. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Aspercreme. TSAC 8383 No Pills :30; TSAC 8395 No Pills :15. 1988 (Box 100)
      - Aspercreme (continued), 1988-1992 (Box 101)
        - 1699. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. 5 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1988 (Box 101)
        - 1700. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. TSAC 9495 Mickee/House :15; TSAC 9505 Tirrell/House :15; TSAC 9515 Cottam/House :15. 1989 (Box 101)
        - 1701. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. TSAC 9475 Lois Tirrell :15. 1989 (Box 101)
        - 1702. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. TSAC 9495 Mickee/House :15; TSAC 9505 Tirrell/House :15; TSAC 9515 Cottam/House :15. 1989 (Box 101)
        - 1703. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. TSAC 9475 Lois Tirrell :15. 1989 (Box 101)
        - 1704. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. TSAC 8445 Joan McKee :15; TSAC 9475 Lois Tirrell :15; TSAC 9485 Kent Cottam Ver. A :15. 1989 (Box 101)
        - 1705. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Aspercreme. TSAC 9485 Kent Cottam/Ver.A :15. 1989 (Box 101)
        - 1706. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. TSAC 2013 Regis Comparative A ABC :30; TSAC 2023 Regis Comparative B CBS/NBC :30. 1992 (Box 101)
        - 1707. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. TSAC 2023 Regis Comparative/B CBS/NBC :30. 1992 (Box 101)
        - 1708. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. TSAC 2013 Regis Comparative A ABC :30; TSAC 2023 Regis Comparative B CBS/NBC :30. 1992 (Box 101)
        - 1709. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. TSAC 2055 Regis :15; TSAC 2065 Regis A :15 NBC/CBS :15. 1992 (Box 101)